{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "1",
      "question": "What nutrient is crucial for healthy skin?",
      "answer_1": "Calcium",
      "answer_2": "Vitamin C",
      "answer_3": "Iron",
      "correct_answer": "2"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "2",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "1",
      "question": "Which activity is effective in reducing stress?",
      "answer_1": "Watching TV",
      "answer_2": "Eating chocolate",
      "answer_3": "Yoga",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "3",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "1",
      "question": "What's a key benefit of staying hydrated?",
      "answer_1": "Clearer skin",
      "answer_2": "Brighter hair color",
      "answer_3": "Stronger nails",
      "correct_answer": "1"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "4",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "2",
      "question": "What food is a good source of calcium for bone health?",
      "answer_1": "Soda",
      "answer_2": "Broccoli",
      "answer_3": "French fries",
      "correct_answer": "2"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "5",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "2",
      "question": "How many hours of sleep are recommended for teens?",
      "answer_1": "4-6 hours",
      "answer_2": "12-14 hours",
      "answer_3": "8-10 hours",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "6",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "2",
      "question": "Which snack is a healthy alternative to chips?",
      "answer_1": "Almonds",
      "answer_2": "Candy",
      "answer_3": "Potato chips",
      "correct_answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "3",
      "question": "What's the main purpose of sunscreen?",
      "answer_1": "Moisturizing the skin",
      "answer_2": "Enhancing tanning",
      "answer_3": "Protecting from UV rays",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "3",
      "question": "Why is it important to include vegetables in your diet?",
      "answer_1": "They taste good",
      "answer_2": "Rich in vitamins and minerals",
      "answer_3": "They make you taller",
      "correct_answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "topic": "Health",
      "Level": "3",
      "question": "How can you maintain a balanced diet?",
      "answer_1": "Only eat one type of food",
      "answer_2": "Skip meals for faster results",
      "answer_3": "Eat a variety of foods in moderation",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "10",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "1",
      "question": "What information should you avoid sharing online?",
      "answer_1": "Personal address",
      "answer_2": "Favorite color",
      "answer_3": "Pet's name",
      "correct_answer": "1"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "11",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "1",
      "question": "What does a strong password typically include?",
      "answer_1": "Your name and birthdate",
      "answer_2": "Simple words like - password123",
      "answer_3": "Combination of letters, numbers, and symbols",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "12",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "1",
      "question": "Why is it important to check privacy settings on social media?",
      "answer_1": "Increase follower count",
      "answer_2": "Control who sees your posts",
      "answer_3": "Get more likes",
      "correct_answer": "2"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "13",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "2",
      "question": "What's a common sign of a phishing attempt on social media?",
      "answer_1": "Regular updates from friends",
      "answer_2": "Random friend requests",
      "answer_3": "Unusual messages asking for personal information",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "14",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "2",
      "question": "How can you deal with cyberbullying on social media?",
      "answer_1": "Block and report the bully",
      "answer_2": "Respond with negativity",
      "answer_3": "Share personal information in retaliation",
      "correct_answer": "1"
    }, 
    {
      "id": "15",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "2",
      "question": "Why should you think before posting pictures online?",
      "answer_1": "To show off your lifestyle",
      "answer_2": "Increase your popularity",
      "answer_3": "Respect for privacy and consent",
      "correct_answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "id": "16",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "3",
      "question": "What is two-factor authentication, and why is it important?",
      "answer_1": "Extra layer of security, requires another verification step",
      "answer_2": "A way to increase your follower count",
      "answer_3": "Only needed for celebrities",
      "correct_answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "id": "17",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "3",
      "question": "How often should you review and update your online passwords?",
      "answer_1": "Once a year is sufficient",
      "answer_2": "Regularly, at least every few months",
      "answer_3": "Never, if it's not broken",
      "correct_answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "id": "18",
      "topic": "Safe Social Media",
      "Level": "3",
      "question": "Why should you be cautious about accepting friend requests from strangers?",
      "answer_1": "Protect yourself from potential scams or danger",
      "answer_2": "Make new friends easily",
      "answer_3": "Increase your follower count for popularity",
      "correct_answer": "1"
    }
 ]
}